tezenis.com 2012-10-15

# Privacy Policy - TEZENIS ITALY

**CALZEDONIA GROUP'S WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for visiting our pages. With this notice we would like to inform you of Calzedonia Group's commitment to safeguarding the privacy of its sites' users and invite you to read the following carefully.

This page describes the rules for managing the Calzedonia Group websites with reference to the personal data of the users consulting it. These sites are accessible by computer starting from the domains and sub-domains registered for each of the Calzedonia Group brands and companies, including by way of example but not limited to:

Pursuant to Article 13 of Italian Legislative Decree 196/03 issued in implementation of Articles 10 and 11 of Directive No. 95/46/EC, this Privacy Policy is also given as a brief statement, where a full one is not shown for that purpose, to those who interact with the Calzedonia Group sites' web services so as to protect personal data that can be accessed by computer. It should be remembered that this statement only applies to the sites referable to the domains and sub-domains registered to Calzedonia Group brands and companies, and not to any other websites that may be linked to such and visited by the user.

The content of this statement has also been prepared in view of Recommendation 2/2001 adopted by the European authorities for the protection of personal data on 17 May 2001 gathered in the Group established by Art. 29 of Directive 95/46/EC. This recommendation specifies certain minimum requirements for collecting personal data on-line and, specifically, when, how and which information data controllers must provide user when accessing internet pages, regardless of the purpose of said access.

By visiting Calzedonia Group websites, you accept the terms and conditions shown below. If you do not accept these terms, we ask you not to access or use the contents and services offered through our websites.

Personal data collected through our sites are processed with automated tools and for the time strictly necessary for the purpose for which they have been collected. We take the appropriate specific security measures to prevent any loss, unlawful or unfair use of data and any unauthorised access.

The personal data provided by users forwarding requests are used solely to perform those requests and are only disclosed to third parties if strictly necessary and functional to this purpose in compliance with the statements made pursuant to Article 13 of Italian Legislative Decree 196/03. The personal data are processed by staff specially appointed to process them within the limits in which that processing may be necessary to perform their duties by carrying out only the necessary operations.

**TYPES OF DATA PROCESSED**

**Data acquired during internet usage**

The computer systems and software procedures used in Calzedonia websites automatically collect certain personal data during normal operation. This transmission is implicit in the use of internet communication protocols. These data are not collected to be associated with identified interested parties, however their very nature may mean that processing and association with data held by third parties could allow for user identification. This type of data includes IP addresses or domain names of the computers used by users connecting to the websites, URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) addresses of the resources requested, the time of the request, the method used in submitting the request to the server, the size of the file obtained as a result, the number code indicating server data response status (successful, error, etc.), and other parameters relating to the user's operating system and computer environment. These data are used for the sole purpose of gathering anonymous statistical data on the use of the sites, and to check correct functioning. The data may be used to verify responsibility in the event of possible computer crime: with the exception of this possibility, at present, the data for web contacts are kept no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which they were collected and subsequently processed.

**Data supplied voluntarily by the user**

The optional, specific and voluntary sending of e-mails to the addresses published on our websites will entail the automatic acquisition of the sender's address, as this is required for reply. Equally, any further personal data included in the e-mails will also be acquired. Optional explicit and voluntary registration through the appropriate web forms on Calzedonia Group sites entails subsequent acquisition of all the data shown in the fields filled in by the user and their processing complies with the contents of the specific statements shown for each individual form.

By sending e-mails to the other e-mail addresses shown on our sites, consent is given for the processing of the data sent for the purposes and in the procedures as of this Privacy Policy.

**COOKIES**

**Session cookies**

A "cookie" is a small text file created by some websites to store information on the user's computer when he or she accesses the site. Cookies are sent by a web server to the user's browser and stored on the latter's computer; they are then re-sent to the website on subsequent visits. Our websites use so-called "session cookies", which reside exclusively in the user's computer memory and are not stored permanently. This means they are deleted when the browser is closed; use is strictly limited to the transmission of session identification data comprising random numbers generated by the server which are needed to allow secure efficient navigation of our sites.

The cookies used in Calzedonia Group websites do not use other computer techniques that may be harmful to the confidentiality of users' internet usage and do not permit the acquisition of their personal identification data. These sites do not use user tracking systems or cookies to transmit information of a personal nature. The user can, at any time, set his/her browser to accept all cookies, some cookies, or refuse them disabling their use by sites.

**Persistent cookies**

Calzedonia Group websites use web analysis services (Google Analytics) provided by third parties, which use "persistent cookies" that reside in a file stored on the hard disk of the user's computer for a set period of time, even after leaving the website. These cookies are used to customise the user's internet usage by targeting his or her interests and improving site navigation. This type of technology allows information on the website pages visited to be collected and recorded anonymously. The data collected in this way do not permit the visitor to be identified and are in no way combined with other information (e.g. personal details provided by the user through the registration form). These data are used solely to track and examine users' site usage and compile statistics anonymously and through the use of aggregated data which are based on the information collected. The user can, at any time, set his or her browser to accept all cookies, some cookies, or totally refuse them disabling their use by sites.

**Google Analytics**

Calzedonia Group websites use [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/), a web analysis service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies that are stored on the user's computer to allow the visited website to analyse how the users use it. The information generated by the cookie on the use of the website visited by the user (including the IP address) is transmitted to Google and stored on Google's servers in the United States. Google will use this information to track and examine the user's website usage, compile reports on the website activities for the site operators and provide other services related to the website activities and internet usage. Google can also transfer this information to third parties where this is prescribed by law or those third parties process that information on behalf of Google. Google will not associate the user's IP address with any other data possessed by Google. The user can at any time refuse to use cookies by selecting the appropriate setting in his or her browser. By using Calzedonia Group websites, the user agrees to the processing of its data by Google for the procedures and purposes indicated above.

It should also be remembered that, with regard to both session and persistent cookies, the user can normally set his or her browser's preferences so that he or she is informed every time a cookie is stored in the computer's memory. At the end of every session the user can in any case delete both the internet usage cache-memory and the collected cookies from the hard disk.

**OPTIONAL SUPPLY OF DATA**

Apart from the provisions for internet usage data, the user is free to provide the necessary personal data for the purpose of executing his or her specific requests. Failure to supply such data may make it impossible to provide the service requested.

In order to provide a complete overview, we would like to remind you that judicial bodies may require some types of data  (not  subject to the routine management of our sites). In this case disclosure by the data controller to those bodies is compulsory.

**COMMUNICATION AND DISCLOSURE**

No internet usage datum is in any way released. With reference to the information generated by the persistent cookies used by Calzedonia Group sites, this is disclosed to Google Inc. within the limits indicated on this page. With reference to the information entered voluntarily by the user through the web forms available on the sites, this will be subjected to communication within the limits of the scopes indicated in the specific statements made for each individual service subject to registration, pursuant to Article 13 of Italian legislative Decree 196/03.

**DATA SUBJECTS' RIGHTS**

Data subjects can exercise the rights provided for by Article 7 of Italian Legislative Decree No. 196/2003 (e.g. request for the origin of the data, their deletion, supplementation, updating, correction, etc.) within the limits and under the conditions provided for by Articles 8, 9 and 10 of the above-mentioned Legislative Decree. You can request further information regarding the treatment from the persons designated by the writers as data controllers in the person of the Area IT Department Manager of Calzedonia S.p.A. domiciled for the appointment at the Controller's registered office or by writing to privacy@calzedonia.it.

**DATA CONTROLLER**

The data controller is Calzedonia S.p.A., registered office in Via Monte Baldo 20, Dossobuono di Villafranca (VR), Italy.
